SZYMON BURAK

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

BYDGOSZCZ

600 179 174 SZYMON.BURAK0031@GMAIL.COM

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have over three years of experience during which I have executed projects for dozens of clients - ranging from simple websites and online stores to advanced web applications. I completed my engineering studies in computer science at Nicolaus Copernicus University in Toruń. I guarantee conscientiousness and selfreliance. The most important aspect of job for me is the opportunity for development and the realization of ambitious projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Nov 2020 - Apr 2022

SKYLO

At Skylo, I was responsible for developing software for websites and ecommerce projects (WordPress, WooCommerce) as well as web applications (React, Express.js, Nest.js). I also handled client communication.

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

Aug 2021 - Dec 2023

EDUEXPERT

As a JavaScript developer, I was responsible for creating educational games, laboratories, and simulations for children and students in the form of web applications. I collaborated with a team of graphic designers and subject matter experts.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Apr 2022 - Present

CODERGASM

In the role of a full-stack developer, I am responsible for creating software using React and Nest.js.

HTML, CSS

JAVASCRIPT

REACT (REDUX, RTK QUERY)

NEXT.JS

NEST.JS

EXPRESS.JS

MYSQL, POSTGRESQL

GATSBY

WORDPRESS

PHP

REACT NATIVE

EDUCATION

ENGINEERING DEGREE

Oct 2019 - Feb 2023

NICOLAUS COPERNICUS UNIVERSITY

Torun

LANGUAGES

POLISH NATIVE SPEAKER

ENGLISH B2

SPANISH A2

Github

Stack Overflow

LinkedIn

I hereby give my consent for the processing of my personal data for the purpose of the recruitment process, in accordance with the Act of May 10, 2018, on the protection of personal data (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000), and in compliance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016, on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (GDPR)